Hello everyone!
I'm Mirai Takahashi from Hyugaizaka 46.
I'm Hinano Uemura.
Today I'm here in Hyogo Prefecture!
Yay!
You know, I was... on a live broadcast the other day.
I was appointed vice-captain of Hyugaizaka 46!
The vice captain of Hyugaizaka 46 is this member!
I will be the vice-captain of Hyugaizaka 46!
I'm Takahashi Mikumi, a member of the Hyugaizaka 463rd class.
I look forward to working with you.
I knew it...
I'm going to take on a lot of responsibility.
I didn't mean for it to happen.
I've been feeling a little vulnerable ever since you said we're like partners.
That's right, we're going to be partners.
This time, we're looking for stores that will support the tour with us, and as our first job, we'll be putting up posters around the country as part of our PR activities.
We have a first assignment: to put up posters around the country as part of our PR activities.
That's an important assignment.
That's right.
First of all, thank you very much for all the applications.
It seems we really received a lot of applications.
This time, I'd like to visit some of the stores
I'm going to visit some of the shops and actually greet them and put up posters.
The reason why we are doing the poster campaign is because we hope that it will be a great opportunity to promote the Hyuga Festival,
I've decided to do the poster pasting campaign again this time.
I am very happy.
It's the place where Nimekute is held. Let's give this Happy Magical Tour some momentum.
I'm off. Let's get some momentum going for this Happy Magical Tour!
I'm off!
Whew!
First of all, we're at HMV Hankyu Nishinomiya Gardens!
Here I am!
Oh, hello!
Hello!
We'd like you to apply.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad to hear that you applied to the Sunshine Store,
I have a poster here,
May we put it up somewhere in the store?
No problem at all.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much,
I hope you are well.
I'm here this time.
Oh!
Look! I see that many of you have come to the top of the page!
Oh, since the prefecture.
Wow, I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Oh, wow!
We have 1,000 super road groups!
That's a lot.
Thank you very much.
Wow!
Yoko's a big fan!
Look at this!
That's great!
My friend!
She has a unique sense of style!
Once you get into it, it's addictive and you can't lose!
I'm sure she'll watch this.
I'm sure you'll love it.
Thank you thank you thank you thank you, I'm sure you'll see this and be delighted. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I'm glad.
I will leave it out.
I will leave a site message.
Yes, sir.
Okay, can I have a moment?
I'm glad. You've been playing it for a long time.
Eh, hey.
Hey.
It's a demon.
He's a demon.
Do you like this song in particular? Do you have a favorite song?
Anything is fine.
I'll watch it alone.
Yes.
Are you watching Shiho Kato?
I am.
Will you be coming on tour?
Are you coming?
She's coming!
He's bringing it, Castor.
Thank you.
Me...
Me.
Me... me...
Hmm...
Next, you'll be the foot or foot massage of a restaurant that specializes in chicken dishes.
I'm not here. I'm sorry.
Good morning.
He's so cute!
You're so cute!
Thank you so much.
Why did you apply for the Sunshine Shop?
A regular customer of ours.
I've been updating you since I was in Saitama Prefecture.
He was looking for a store in Hyogo Prefecture.
So I applied for the job.
How long have you been a fan of Kinekizaka?
I just found out about Kato Shiga Center. I happened to see him on TV and fell in love at first sight.
Yesterday at the Ria Aminiam.
Oh, wow!
This year's
Oh, I didn't know that.
He's here.
May I write something about you?
I did.
Oh, I'm nervous because it's episode 8 today.
I'm already looking forward to seeing you today.
Hey, it's pretty bad.
By the way, can I ask you about your favorite song? Boo boo!
I'm studying in the morning and I listen to it when I'm studying.
I'll give it to you. I'll talk about it.
I'll tell you about it.
How's it going?
I'll go put it up.
You sure you want it in a prominent place?
I'd like it if you could.
Here we go.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Lovely, Gutensha and everyone.
So warm.
And I was so happy to see how our relationship is expanding from our customers.
Heh.
I was very happy to see that the relationship has been growing since last year, with the Hinatazaka Holcik and others.
I love the Hinatazaka Holcic, where we've been gathering since last year, and I'm very happy that we've been able to expand our relationship.
I'm going to the entrance.
I'm going to go to the entrance.
I heard that you've recently fallen in love with us.
You've been to a lot of our shows, haven't you?
Yes, I love live performances.
I'm glad.
I'll be in the most prominent place. Yes, I love live music.
I'm glad. I'll be in the most prominent place.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
You recently fell in love with us.
Have you seen them live yet?
I've never seen them live.
We're both going to Hyogo.
You're coming?
Did you find him? Please come, this time with this guy and that guy?
That's a surprise.
That's great. He even wrote down the name of the restaurant.
I'd like to have a drink.
I'd love a drink.
May I? Yes, please.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
May I?
I'll have the purple sweet potato milk, please.
I'll have strawberry milk, please.
With strawberry ski.
I'm looking forward to it.
Before I came, I did research.
Once again, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure that everyone from the sun will be here, and I'm sure that you will have sweets and things like that.
I'm sure you'll be on social media a lot.
I would be happy if you all could join me in making this event a success.
Thank you very much.
Sweets
Sweet and tasty
What do you think? It's my first time.
I was a little nervous at first.
But I was touched by everyone's warmth.
And then, the people of the sun went back to that store.
And that's how the circle of the sun is expanding.
I thought it was really wonderful.
I'm looking forward to working with them on the national tour.
It's important to visit the stores.
It's important.
There are so many things that you can't understand unless you actually see them with your own eyes.
You can't just send out messages on SNS or blogs.
You can't just send out messages on social networking sites or blogs.
We can do what we can do.
But it's really important to give people the opportunity to learn about hygiene
It's important.
I think it's important to have a chance to see our members in action.
I think it would be great if we could promote the local area.
Why did you get a little embarrassed at the end?
I shouldn't be so serious when I talk about these things.
It's a good thing.
Well, you cried, that's unusual.
But you know what?
You were the first one to come.
He's already hosting a party around me.
He said...
As a fellow member of the group...
I'm worried about young Kon-chan.
The four of us are really one.
That's right.
We're all four of us.
We have to share everything.
She said she'd carry all our stuff.
But to Mr. Mirei...
You're captains too, aren't you?
“You're captain Fukuhuku too!
I'm Captain Fuku Fuku, and you're Captain Fuku Fuku, and I'm Captain Fuku Fuku.
I'm Fukufuku captain, but there are three of us.
I'm counting on you
I'm counting on you too
Thank you
Next stop: Hirota JR Kobe
We're going to Kobe Troughcon.
This is Kobe Station.
According to the map, it's about 30 minutes from the venue.
It looks like it's about 30 minutes from the venue.
I guess it's close to the venue, so I thought it might be a place where many people come.
Hello.
Hello. I'm sorry to bother you.
Who applied this time?
Thank you very much.
Why did you apply this time?
Because I was originally interested in Debbie and Hinatazaka from the time of their debut.
Since their debut?
Since then, thank you very much.
And Yuki, for your support this time around.
I thought I'd support this store as well.
Thank you very much.
Have you ever been to a live concert at Hyuugaizaka?
I've been many times.
How many?
How many were there just now?
We're at the studio in Inada.
Oh, to Inada's studio.
To Inazaki. Thank you very much.
Oh, I'm so glad.
By the way...
I'm talking about the inside of a locker.
Hiyori Hamanishi.
Hiyotan?
Absolutely.
Hiyotan.
Thank you very much for the closing.
You can write a message on the poster and put it up.
Thank you very much.
How about you put it up here? Thank you very much for coming.
I'll write it down for you.
I'll write it down.
I called you.
Thank you very much.
I'm the one who got it.
You applied.
Thank you very much.
I'll always go once.
Oh, you're coming to Kobe?
I'm going to Kobe.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Kobe.
Kobe.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
We'll do our best to make it to Kobe.
Then we'll go to Kobe Fugetsudo Honmachi Honten.
I'll be there.
After all, we have a song called “Gaufre and You
I know I have to come here.
And I'm glad because it's a three-period song.
I wonder if the store owner knows it.
This?
It's big.
It's huge!
Oh my God, this? It's huge! It's huge! Oh, my God!
Wow! It says “Michala” on it!
Can you see it?
Can't you see it? You can't see it?
It says “Fugetsudo” on it.
You're amazing! He's amazing!
Oh, wow! It's so big!
It looks like our customers feel free to shop with us, and we are happy to apply for the prize. Thank you very much.
He's just singing,
I'm Sei Suzuki.
Thank you very much.
Well, I have a connection with you,
I would like to write a report star and put it up.
Thank you very much.
I'll be happy to use your desk,
Let's go.
Cute.
Thank you very much.
Have you heard of Hinatazaka? Hinatazaka 46.
Interesting.
Thank you very much.
Please buy the magazine.
Thank you very much. I'm glad. Thank you very much. I wasn't expecting any customers.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I really like the third graders.
I'm so glad
Of course we're past five minutes
You know me, don't you?
Yay!
I'm so happy for him.
I'm glad he's in his third year, because this is really great timing.
Live?
It's a lot of attention, it's fun.
I went to the Scilly time, and I've been doing PR, and it's been great attention, and I want to get in, so I guess that's what this is all about, right?
We want to get in, so that's what we're doing. We're doing PR, and we want people to come to the show.
It's done!
Thank you very much.
You're an apple.
Apples.
Apples on Third Street.
Two apple buns in a ring!
It seems to be limited to the main store on the street, so I hope you all enjoy it!
me
Me... me...
Hey, you two, I'm going to eat a Kulakula!
Next, we went to the flower and balloon store
Blossom Kobe Sunmania store!
Here we are!
This is the shop that we use to send off flowers and celebrate live concerts.
We get a lot of requests from fans for flowers for send-offs and concerts.
Fans often ask us to deliver them to them.
I heard that they sometimes deliver them to us.
So we are very grateful to them for their kindness.
This entrance is very stylish.
Look how stylish!
Excuse me for interrupting.
It smells good.
Who submitted the application?
Thank you very much, ma'am.
I'd be happy to share it with you.
Please do.
Thank you very much.
Why are you applying for the Ohisama Store this time?
Well, following the last Kobe show, this time we are receiving orders from many OHISAN
We learned that you were working on this kind of project.
We would like to support them through our flowers, so we decided to support them.
Thank you very much.
When did you start to mention flowers to Hinoto?
Well, it's not like that.
That's about right.
Since a long time ago. Thank you very much.
Do you think I'm in it?
I think you're in.
I mean, you just got in.
Yes, yes, I am.
I'm glad.
It's been a long time.
Well, since you're here, why don't you sign a poster or write a message or something?
Please, please, please, this is a project. Can I pay you to sign a poster or write a message?
Yes, please.
It's for merchandise.
The new ones.
I'm here. Great. Thank you.
You won all of them.
I won one yesterday.
What? Yesterday?
Yesterday? You got it? How's it going?
Thank you very much.
I'll write it down, and it'll be warm. Thank you very much.
Red.
Thank you.
It's warm.
Cute.
There's a cat
Maru-chan
Oh, there's Meimei-san
That means
Meimei-san is
Spring
What kind of memory does your sister have for him, asking him not to fall asleep?
Oh, really?
Please catch him...
Heh heh heh heh
He's cute.
Did he catch it?
Yes, I did.
I love it.
Okay, the second one.
Yes, we have a specialty store here. I'll let you talk to them.
Thank you very much.
Yes!
Are you going to be there? Are you leaving, Kan-chan?
Do you want to carry it?
It's heavy.
Look, there's Haru-chan!
Funny thing.
Since you're here...
Thank you very much.
I'm glad
Thank you
We received flowers.
We will decorate your house.
Lovely.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Please keep them coming.
Thank you very much for today.
See you later, Anchan.
See you later.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
See you today.
Yes, the sun has set.
We've finished all our PR activities.
Thank you for your hard work.
You've done a lot of traveling.
How was it? It was Hinano-san's first time.
Yes, it was.
I really felt everyone's warmth.
I was really touched by everyone's warmth and love.
I got so much power from it.
I hope we can bring this power to you again on the tour.
I hope we can deliver this power to you again on the tour.
It was so encouraging to have you next to me.
What?
One by one?
Me too, today was my first time as captain.
How did you like it?
I hope this makes you excited about the tour.
I want you to look forward to the tour even more.
I also wanted this to be an opportunity for you to look forward to the future of Hinatazaka 46.
But it wasn't about what my role was.
I think there are new connections that are created by the members bringing the tour to Japan, so we will continue to do our best to make the whole country excited.
Hinataka46 will continue to do our best.
So please continue to support us!
If you like this video, please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
See you on the tour!